Oh hi there, welcome to a day in the life of Tom Holland on the set of...
Enchanted.
Let's do this.
Day 457.
It feels like that.
In the morning, a lot of my exes are as crazy as possible.
It's a challenge, Rachel.
How are you?
Good morning.
Alright.
You well?
Yeah, pretty good.
Pretty good.
Yeah?
Morning affair.
Hello Rachel!
Hi!
Smile, you're on camera.
Oh, here we are in the make chair, very important part of the process.
It's always good.
And three, two, one, go.
He's not got one, he's got two.
You alright, mate?
All good, Tom?
Lexi, help!
That's pure shade.
What you two?
Yeah.
Go do some stunts or something.
You alright?
So I hanging on like that, and I pull the cord, and the cannon goes.
We get to it.
Cool.
That be a great day.
Yeah, it be fun.
Love it.
We'll see you out there.
See you out there, mate.
Harry, we're ready for talk.
Go on then.
This is Rick Lipton.
He helps me with my accent.
This is Anthony Druitt.
He's in charge of costume.
This is Brian, our first AD.
This is Tom Bentley, second AD.
Hi guys.
This is Gary Dawson, in charge of...
property.
Ready and...
Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang.
I don't know if I'm going to be able to do that, guys.
And so again, this is a very early one, but it shows kind of what we were thinking.
I think that sometimes people forget that making tea is an art form.
We bring our own tea bags from Yorkshire, and I get criticised a lot online, especially for the way I make tea.
This misconception that I use too much milk, it cuts so deep because it what I do for a living.
This is the conception, this is the boat in which Nate and Sully are trying to steal.
I feel like Homelander.
I am down here fighting an obscene amount of people.
Did we get it?
No, we didn't get it.
We're moving on?
No, we're not moving on.
Alright, I'll be in my trailer, guys.
So we've just wrapped day 732 of Uncharted.
That was a typical day for us.
Always a lot of fun, a lot of laughs.
I hope you enjoyed a little insight into what it's actually like to make a film.
And I hope you enjoy the movie.